jobplacements.com 2017-06-06

# Job Placements - Privacy Policy

Job Placements Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site and upload your CV. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter inter alia, your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you job information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

To stop receiving our emails, please click the link found at the bottom of each email or update your account preferences under 'Alerts' from the main dashboard.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users that are based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites across the Internet.

Users may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

The cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on www.jobplacements.com. You may opt out of some third-party vendors' use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.jobplacements.com/disclaimer.php

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.jobplacements.com/). Jobplacements.com is owned by Locker Leisure Limited located at 923 Finchley Road, London, NW11 7PE.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

http://www.jobplacements.com

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to [Zendesk](http://www.rhinosupport.com/zendesk.htm) and save!
